Edwin Bediakoh Ashie

(+233) 208430088

Email address: edwinashie289@gmail.com

Website: https://eddieash0007.github.io/portfolio/

(+233) 20 843 0088

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/edwin-ashie-117462116/

ABOUT ME

I am a trained Certified Professional Ethical Hacker with expertise in building web applications and teaching. I have a MSc degree in Information Technology (IT) with over two years of working experience working in the field of IT. I am eager to be challenged to grow and further improve my IT skills. My greatest passion is in life is using my technical know-how to benefit other people and organizations

WORK EXPERIENCE

Teaching Assistant

Ghana Technology University College [08/2018 - 09/2019]

City: Accra Country: Ghana

- ° Taught C++ programing to first and second year students.
- Handling of Visual Basic Programming tutorials to third-year students.
- ° Taught computer networking to second-year students.
- ° Taught AI to final year students.
- ° Helped organize a training session to introduce first-year students to mobile application development.

IT End User Technology Personnel (Intern)

ABSA Bank Ghana (formerly Barclays) [04/2017 - 06/2017]

City: Accra Country: Ghana

Department: Technology

- ° Configuration of hardware and software within the bank.
- Migrating Clients devices from legacy systems to Fusion Systems.
- ° Anti-virus remediation for client devices and servers.
- ° Troubleshooting issues associated with IT infrastructure within the bank.

IT End User Technology Personnel (Intern)

ABSA Bank Ghana (formerly Barclays) [03/2016 - 06/2016]

City: Accra

Country: Ghana

Department: Technology

- ° Configuration of hardware and software within the bank.
- Migrating Clients devices from legacy systems to Windows 7 (Fusion Systems).
- ° AV remediation for client devices and servers.
- ° Troubleshooting issues associated with IT infrastructure within the bank.

IT Applications Support Personnel (Intern)

ABSA Bank Ghana (formerly Barclays) [03/2015 - 06/2015]

City: Accra Country: Ghana

Department: Technology

• Management of user accounts for multiple business applications used within the bank

EDUCATION

MSc Information Technology

Kwame Nkrumah University of Science and Technology [10/2019 - 11/2021]

Address: Accra Rd, Kumasi (Ghana)

www.knust.edu.gh

BSc Information Technology

Ghana Technology University College [09/2014 – 07/2018] **Address:** North Industrial Area, Nsawam Rd, Accra (Ghana) site.gtuc.edu.gh

General Science

St Peters Senior High [10/2011 - 04/2014]

Address: Nkwatia, Kwahu (Ghana)

SKILLS

Programming Stack

Laravel / Python / HTML5/CSS/ JavaScript / Tailwind CSS / IONIC / MySQL

Document Processing & Design

Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft PowerPoint, Microsoft Outlook / Adobe Photoshop

System Administration

Linux

CERTIFICATIONS & TRAINING

MITRE ATT&CK Defender (MAD) ATT&CK Cyber Threat Intelligence

Cybrary [07/2021]

Wireshark: Packet Analysis and Ethical Hacking: Core Skills

Udemy [07/2021]

Certified Professional Ethical Hacker (CPEH)

e-crime Bureau [06/2021]

Kali Linux for Ethical Hackers and Pentesters

Whizlabs [12/2020]

Cybersecurity Essentials

CISCO [07/11/2020]

Introduction to Cybersecurity

CISCO [23/10/2020]

AWS Business Essentials

Udemy [23/10/2020]

REFEREES

Head; Systems Support

Name: Seth Amarteifio

Phone number: (+233) 202017561 Email: sethamarteifio@gmail.com

ABSA Bank Ghana

Head; Department of Mobile Computing

Name: Dr Lempogo Forgor

Phone number: (+233) 202698192 Email: <u>f.lempogo@gctu.edu.gh</u>

Ghana Communication Technology University